{
    "subject": "Elena_Glinskaya",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Vasili_III_of_Russia",
    "human_readable": "Elena Glinskaya is married to Vasili III of Russia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9843504428863525,
            "question": "Was Vasili III married to Elena Glinskaya?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8890398144721985,
            "question": "Who is Elena Glinskaya married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8803709149360657,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Elena Glinskaya and Vasili III?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8283389806747437,
            "question": "To whom was Elena Glinskaya wed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6929084062576294,
            "question": "What is the name of Vasili III's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47516152262687683,
            "question": "Who was the Tsar of Russia during Elena Glinskaya's lifetime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4730854332447052,
            "question": "How did Elena Glinskaya influence Russian history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3573393225669861,
            "question": "What is known about Elena Glinskaya's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3487117886543274,
            "question": "When did Vasili III rule Russia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26493725180625916,
            "question": "Were there any notable events during Vasili III's reign?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Elena Glinskaya is married to Vasili III of Russia.",
            "html": "yago_30105_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Vasili III rule Russia?",
            "html": "yago_30105_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Elena Glinskaya's life?",
            "html": "yago_30105_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did Elena Glinskaya influence Russian history?",
            "html": "yago_30105_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30105_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30105_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30105_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30105_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30105_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30105_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30105_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30105_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30105_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30105_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because the documents mention that Elena Glinskaya was married to Vasily III, and also refer to her as his wife multiple times. The information in the documents supports the triple \"Elena Glinskaya is married to Vasili III of Russia\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the marriage between Elena Glinskaya and Vasily III, indicating that they were indeed married. For example, one document states, \"In January 1526 Vasily III married Elena Vasiliyevna Glinskaya,\" which supports the statement that Elena Glinskaya is married to Vasili III of Russia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}